Guide to the Robert E. Butts Papers, 1908-1997 ASP.2000.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Professional Materials, 1951-1997; II.
  - Research, Writing, and Publication, 1951-1996; 1.
    - Works Authored and Edited by Butts: Correspondence and Administrative Documents, 1970-1986; 3.
      This section contains mainly correspondence concerning the specific publication projects and related administrative documents, not the drafts of the publications themselves.
      - The Cambridge Dictionary of Philosophy, ed. Audi, Cambridge University Press (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - The Canadian Encyclopedia, New Canadian Encyclopedia Publishing (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - A Companion to Metaphysics, ed. Sosa and Kim, Blackwell (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - A Companion to the Philosophy of Science, ed. Newton-Smith, Blackwell (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Constructivism and Science: Essays in Recent German Philosophy, ed. Butts and Brown, Kluwer (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Dictionary of Scientific Biography, ed. Gillespie, Scribner (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - The Epistemological Assumptions of Four Great Physicists, ed. John T. Blackmore (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - "The Grammar of Reason: Hamann's Challenge to Kant" in Synthese (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - The International Who's Who of Intellectuals, International Biography Center (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Kant and the Double Government Methodology, Italian Translation by Mary Fornai (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - "Kant's Theory of Musical Sound: An Early Exercise in Cognitive Science" in Dialogue (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Logic and the Workings of the Mind, ed. Falkenstein (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Metaphysische Anfangsgründe der Naturwissenschaft, trans. Butts and Friedman (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - The Methodological Heritage of Newton, ed. Butts and Davis, University of Toronto Press (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - "On Buchdahl's and Palter's Papers" in Synthese 23, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Philosophia (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - "Philosophy of Science in Canada" in Ruch Filozoficzny Kwartalnik (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Project Pragmatik Published by Felix Meiner Verlag, 1982-1986 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Reader to Nicholas Rescher's "System of Pragmatic Idealism" (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Routledge Encyclopedia of Philosophy, ed. Craig, Routledge (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Science, Decision, and Value, ed. Butts, Leach, and Pearce, Reidel (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - "Sciences and Pseudosciences: An Attempt at a New Form of Demarcation" in Earman et al., ed., University of Pittsburgh Press (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - "Scientific Progress: The Laudan Manifesto" in Philosophy of Social Science (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - The Scientific Revolution: An Encyclopedia, ed. Applebaum (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - "Teleology and Scientific Method in Kant's Critique of Judgement" in NOUS (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - William Whewell's Theory of Scientific Method, ed. Butts, University of Pittsburgh Press/Hackett (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - General Correspondence re: Publishing (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Unidentified Correspondence re: Possibility of Butts Anthology (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Reviews of William Whewell's Theory of Scientific Method, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - Reviews of New Perspectives on Galileo, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - Reviews of Proceedings of the 5th International Congress of Logic, Methodology, and Philosophy of Science, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      - Reviews of The Methodological Heritage of Newton, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - Review of Kant's Philosophy of Physical Science, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Kant and the Double Government Methodology: Supersensibility and Method in Kant's Philosophy of Science: Drafts, Correspondence, and Reviews, 1982-1990; 4.
      This section contains drafts for Butts' published work Kant and the Double Government Methodology, as well as related documents such as reviews, correspondence, and permission to publish requests.
      - Preface I: "An Ordinary Preface," Typescript (Box 12a, Folder 1)
      - "Preface II: Points of Reference," Typescript (Box 12a, Folder 2)
      - "Preface I and II," Typescript with Handwritten Corrections (Box 12a, Folder 3)
      - "Introduction," Typescript (Box 12a, Folder 4)
      - Chapter I: "Metaphysical Explanation in Leibniz: The Monads," Typescript (Box 12a, Folder 5)
      - Chapter II: "Leibniz On the Side of Angels," Typescript (Box 12a, Folder 6)
      - Chapter III: "Kant, ESP, and the Inaugural Disseration" (Box 12a, Folder 7)
      - Chapter IV: "Soemmering and Euler: Space and the Soul" (Box 12a, Folder 8)
      - Chapter V: "Kant: Space and the Soul" (Box 12a, Folder 9)
      - Chapter VI: "Rules, Images and Constructions: Kan'ts Constructive Idealism" (Box 12a, Folder 10)
      - Chapter VII: "Two Fundamental Principles of Methodology" (Box 12a, Folder 11)
      - Chapter VIII: "Hypotheses in Science" (Box 12a, Folder 12)
      - Chapter IX: "The Restauration of Teleology" (Box 12a, Folder 13)
      - "Central Nervous System: Philosophers as Dieticians of the Mind" (Box 12b, Folder 1)
      - Table of Contents, Preface and Excerpts (Box 12b, Folder 2)
      - Chapter Fragments (Box 12b, Folder 3)
      - "Seeing Ghosts: Immanuel Kant's Investigation of Mental Disorders and the Paranormal", 1982 (Box 12b, Folder 4)
      - Bibliography: References to Works of Kant (Box 12b, Folder 5)
      - Indexes and Bibliographies for KDGM (Box 12b, Folder 6)
      - Notes and Articles on Kant by Butts and Others (Box 12b, Folder 7)
      - Anonymous Review of KDGM (Box 12b, Folder 8)
      - Publication Guidelines by the University of Toronto Press (Box 12b, Folder 9)
      - Permission Requests for KDGM, 1983-1984 (Box 12b, Folder 10)
      - Reviews of and Responses to KGDM, 1984-1990 (Box 12b, Folder 11)
    - Research, 1951-1992; 5.
      - CVs (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Lists of Publications and Presentations, 1984-1994 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Material Related to CVs and Publication Lists (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Unidentified Bibliographies and Indices (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - A Selective Bibliography on Kant by Ralph C.S. Walker, 2nd Edition, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Bibliography of Kant Literature for 1987, Part II and for 1988, Part I (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Bibliography of Kant Literature for 1989, Part IV (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Bibliography of Kant Literature for 1991, Part IV and for 1992, Part II (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - A Bibliography of William Whewell, 1814-1900 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Charts and Tables (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence and Forms re: Research Grants, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Edward C. Pickering and the Transformation of American Astronomy, 1840-1920 (Project Description) (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Philosophical Views of Scientific Change: The History of the Ice Age Hypothesis, 1830-1880 (Book Proposal) (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Mechanisms of Value-Change in Science (Draft Prospectus) (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous/Unidentified Notes (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - The Criterion of Cognitive (Empirical) Significance to the Verificationist Principle (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Mill's Argument for the Triviality of Prediction, Logic bk. III, ch. XIV, 6 (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Inserts 1-5 on Kant's Critique of Pure Reason and the History of Modern Natural Science (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - A Suggested Reconstruction of the Argument of the 2nd Analogy (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Kant: The Four Moments of a Judgement of Taste (des Geschmacksurteils) (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Physics III (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Epistemology in the Aufbau (Notes on a Talk by M. Friedman) (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Methodological Components of Scientific Theory (A Kantian Formulation) (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Notes on Similarity and Equality, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Notes on Specification, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Introductory Remarks on Critique of Judgement (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Kant, Hamann, Schelling, and Jung: The Rhetoric and Psychology of Symbolism (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Van Fraassen and Realism/Anti-Realism (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Bas's Constructive Empiricism (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Socialism (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Analysis of Meanings of Two Terms Prominent in Social and Political Thinking (Dr. Ward) (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Bentham (Notes), September 29, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - J.S. Mill - Essays on Nature, Utility of Religion (1859), and Theism (1870) (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - The Perennial Social Tension: 'I' and/or 'We': An Examination Into the Pertinence of J.S. Mills' Essay on Liberty (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Herbert Spencer, First Principles (1864) (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Herbert Spencer, Transcendental Philosophy (1857) (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - J.S. Mill - System of Logic ("The Canons of Induction" - bk. III, ch. VIII) (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - J.S. Mill, On Liberty (Outline of Contents) (Box 13, Folder 38)
      - J.S. Mill - On the Logic of the Moral Sciences (Book VI, Logic) (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 39)
      - Mechanics - Newton, Mach, Kant (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 40)
      - Leibniz Cohesion (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 41)
      - The Conceptual Framework of Kant's Philosophy of Science (Notes) (Box 13, Folder 42)
      - Letter to Qualiton Imports, Ltd. re: Glass Harmonica Recordings, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 43)
      - Introduction for David Savan: "Postmodernist Philosophy and Nietzsche" - University of Western Ontario, March 1987 (Box 13, Folder 44)
      - Comments on L.L. Laudan, "William Whewell on the Consilience of Inductions" (Box 13, Folder 45)
      - Critique of Pure Reason 1781-1981, Faculty of Arts, March 10, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 46)
      - The Worlds of Kant - Leibniz Conference, November 1982 (Box 13, Folder 47)
      - Comments on Gregory Good, "Method, Science, and the Historical Approach" - History of Science Society, Norwalk, CT, October 1983 (Box 13, Folder 48)
      - Comment: Glenn Hartz, "Kant's Mature Metaphysic of Matter" - American Philosophical Association, St. Louis, MO, May 1986 (Box 13, Folder 49)
      - Comments on Michael Ruse, "William Whewell and the Argument from Design" - Canadian Philosophical Association, June 1974 (Box 13, Folder 50)
      - Comments on David Wilson "A Physicist's Alternative to Materialism" - History of Science Society Annual Meeting, Norwalk, CT, October 1983 (Box 13, Folder 51)
      - Comments on Paul Theerman "Maxwell and Method" - History of Science Society Annual Meeting, Norwalk, CT, October 1983 (Box 13, Folder 52)
      - Research Notes on Whewell: Notebook I (Box 13a, Folder 1)
      - Research Notes on Whewell: Notebook II (Box 13a, Folder 2)
      - Research Notes on Whewell: Notebook III (Box 13a, Folder 3)
      - Research Notes on Whewell: Notebook IV (Box 13a, Folder 4)
      - Research Notes on Whewell: Notebook V (Box 13a, Folder 5)
  - Teaching, 1954-1997; 2.
    The items in this subseries document Butts' function as an instructor and faculty member at various institutions, particularly the University of Western Ontario. The majority of the documents pertaining to the courses that Butts taught are in the form of teaching notes, handouts, and syllabi (Section 1). Also included is a small amount of correspondence and other administrative records that relate to Butts' employment and his role as a member of the university community outside of his academic function.
    - Instructional Materials, 1968-1991; 1.
      - Nipissing University College (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Seminar in 19th-Century Philosophy, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Kant Seminar (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Realism (Konstanz) (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Seminar on Leibniz (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Witchcraft Syllabi (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Witchcraft Notes and Readings (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Witchcraft Exams (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Witchcraft (T.M. Lennon) (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - The Social Philosophy of Herbert Spencer (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Theories of Scientific Method: Mill and Whewell, Fall 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Transparencies (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Notes from Anthropology from a Pragmatic Point of View (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - The Principles of Monadic Change and Its Relation to Physics (Notes), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Leibniz' Monadology (Notes), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Heidegger on the Leading Distinctions of the Identity Philosophy (Notes) (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Outline of Boehme's System (Notes) (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Kant's Theory of Scientific Method (Notes) (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Schelling's Absolute Idealism (Notes) (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - The Two Philosophies of the Antinomies (Notes) (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Kant and 19th-Century Views of Science (Notes) (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Kant's Metaphysical Foundations of Natural Science (Notes), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - "Science and the Humanities: A Historical and Analytic Comparison" (Notes), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - "Dilthey: The Critique of Historical Reason" (Notes) (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Nietzsche on Truth (Notes) (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - "The Mind/Body Problem: The Importance of Its Solution for the Creation of Human Sciences" (Notes), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Schelling/Witchcraft Reading (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Of Reasoning and Of Induction(Readings) (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous/Unidentified Teaching Notes and Materials (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Administrative Materials, 1954-1997; 2.
      - Job Applications, 1980-1987 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Visiting Lectures/Appointments, 1982-1986 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - University of Pittsburgh, 1987-1997 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - University of Western Ontario, 1978-1996 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Nipissing University College, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - University of Konstanz, 1984-1995 (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - Job Offer from St. Lawrence University (Telegram), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Performance Reviews, 1981-1991 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - University of Oslo, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Professional Organizations and Conferences, 1963-1997; 3.
    This subseries consists of correspondence, newsletters, pamphlets, financial records, meeting minutes, and other items that document Butts' active role in his professional community. He served on boards and in leadership positions for several of the professional organizations and conferences represented in these records, notably chairing several committees of the International Union of the History and Philosophy of Science during the 1970s and 1980s. He was particularly active in the international philosophical community, organizing and attending conferences in Europe, Canada, and the United States throughout his career.
    - Professional Organizations, 1963-1997; 1.
      - Association for the Advancement of Science in Canada (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Association for Foundations of Science, Language, and Cognition, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Canadian Academic Centre in Italy, Newsletter, May 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2a)
      - Canadian Federation for the Humanities (CFH), 1982-1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Canadian Philosophical Association (CPA), 1977-1988 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Canadian Political Science Association Bulletin, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Canadian Science and Technology Historical Association, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Canadian Society for History and Philosophy of Science (CSHPS), 1979-1986 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Canadian Society for History and Philosophy of Science "Communique", 1979-1997 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - History of Science Society (HSS), 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - History of Science and Technology in Canada Bulletin, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Interamerican Council for Research on Science Policy, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - International Committee for the History of Technology (ICOHTEC), 1977-1986 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - International Council of Scientific Unions, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - International Council of Scientific Unions Newsletters, 1980-1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - International Union of History and Philosophy of Science (IUHPS) Brochure, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Canadian National Committee, International Union of History and Philosophy of Science (CNC/IUHPS) Minutes and Agendas, 1978-1991 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Canadian National Committee, International Union of History and Philosophy of Science (CNC/IUHPS) General Correspondence, 1978-1988 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Division of History of Science, International Union of History and Philosophy of Science (DHS/IUHPS) (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Division of History of Science, International Union of History and Philosophy of Science (DHS/IUHPS) Bulletins, 1976-1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Division of History of Science, International Union of History and Philosophy of Science (DHS/IUHPS) Newsletters, 1978-1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Division of Logic, Methodology and Philosophy of Science, International Union of History and Philosophy of Science (DLMPS/IUHPS) General Correspondence, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Division of Logic, Methodology and Philosophy of Science, International Union of History and Philosophy of Science (DLMPS/IUHPS) Finances and Proceedings, 1971-1985 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Institute for the History of Arabic Science Newsletters, March 1978-September 1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Leibniz Society (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - North American Kant Society (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - PRISMA (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Progressive Conservative Task Force on Taxation, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council of Canada: Council Update, Jules and Gabrielle Léger Fellowship, April 1985 (Box 16, Folder 10a)
    - Conferences, 1969-1996; 2.
      - 13th Annual Congress of the Canadian Philosophical Association, Toronto, ON, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - 3rd International Kant Congress, Rochester, NY, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Foundations of Scientific Method: The 19th Century, Bloomington, IN, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Biennial Meeting of the Philosophy of Science Association, Lansing, MI, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - 1st International Conference on the History and Philosophy of Science, Jyvaskyla, Finland, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - The Heritage of Kant: A Conference in Celebration of the 250th Anniversary of the Birth of Kant, Kalamazoo, MI, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Ottawa Congress on Kant, Ottawa, ON, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - 5th International Congress of Logic, Methodology and Philosophy of Science, London, ON, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - 5th International Congress of Logic, Methodology and Philosophy of Science Bulletins and Programs, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Institute in the Philosophy of Science, Banff, AB, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Workshop in the History and Philosophy of Science, Benmiller, ON, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Conference on the Study of the History of Canadian Science and Technology, Kingston, ON, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - 2nd International Colloquium on History and Philosophy of Science, Pisa, Italy, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - 6th International Congress of Logic, Methodology and Philosophy of Science, Hanover, Germany, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Lewis White Beck Kant Conference, Rochester, NY, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - National Seminar on Science and Technology in India in the 18th-19th Century, New Delhi, India, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Workshop on Scientific Change, Pittsburgh, PA, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - 3rd International Conference of History and Philosophy of Science, Montreal, QC, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Canadian Society for History and Philosophy of Science, Montreal, QC, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - University of Ottowa Philosophy Colloquia, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Leibniz: The Philosophy and Foundations of Science, Toronto, ON, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Baylor University Victorian Conference, Waco, TX, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - 1st Annual Conference on Philosophy of Science, Center for Philosophy of Science, University of Pittsburgh, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Blacksburg, Notes on Niiniluoto and Others, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Conference on 1883, Toronto, ON, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - 7th International Congress of Logic, Methodology and Philosophy of Science, Salzburg, Austria, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Latin American Symposium of Mathematical Logic, Caracas, Venezuela, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Philosophy of Science Association (PSA), Chicago, IL, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Learned Societies Conference, Montreal, QC, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Thought and Language in Enlightened Philosophy: An International Conference in 17th and 18th Century Philosophy, Toronto, ON, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - 17th International Congress of History of Science, Berkeley, CA, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - 6th International Kant Congress, State College, PA, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Learned Societies Conference, Manitoba, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - On the Leibniz Renaissance: The Reasons for Contemporary Interest in Leibniz' Thought, Florence, Italy, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Conference on the History and Philosophy of Science, Edinburgh, Scotland, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - International Committee for the History of Technology (ICOHTEC) "Dresden Symposium", 1986 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - "The Dubrovnik Seminars," Dubrovnik, Yugoslavia, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - 8th International Congress of Logic, Methodology and Philosophy of Science, Moscow, USSR, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Oxford CPS Conference, Oxford, England, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - 7th Joint Meeting of the Divisions of History of Science and Philosophy of Science, International Union of History and Philosophy of Science (IUHPS), Coimbra, Portugal, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - National History of Science Societies Meeting, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Baden-Württemberg Seminars, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Annual Congress of the Canadian Philosophical Association, Quebec, QC, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - 18th International Congress of the History of Science, Hamburg and Munich, Germany, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Learned Societies Congress, Victoria, BC, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - Spindel Conference, Memphis, TN, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 39)
      - Comments on Michael Friedman: 'Regulative and Constitutive' for Spindel Conference, Memphis, TN, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 40)
      - Conference on the Works of Onora O'Neill, South Bend, IN, September 1991 (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - Kant and Contemporary Epistemology, Florence, Italy, May 1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Seminar for Medieval and Renaissance Studies: Witchcraft and Magic in the Middle Ages and the Renaissance, London, ON, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Logic and the Workings of the Mind, London, ON, May 1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - 8th International Kant Congress, Memphis, TN, March 1995 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - 3rd Quadrennial International Fellows Conference, Castiglioncello, Italy, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - German-American Interaction in Scientific Philosophy After 1933: An International Conference, Pittsburgh, PA, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - The Methodological Heritage of Newton, London, ON (Box 18, Folder 7)